[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とまります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Залишитись (на ночівлю)"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'れんしゅう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Тренування"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せんたく' read in word?",
        "answer": "Прання"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そうじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Прибирання"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はじまります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Починається"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんがた' read in word?",
        "answer": "Новий тип, стиль"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひらきます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відчиняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зал, приміщення"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たのしみます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Насолоджуватися, розважатися"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おおどおり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Проспект, головна дорога"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вищезазначене, понад, більше"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぞう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Статуя"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けいば' read in word?",
        "answer": "Стрибки на конях"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'きょうりゅう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Динозавр"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たてもの' read in word?",
        "answer": "Будівля"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うつします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Знімати(відео), робити(фото), робити репродукцію"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えいぞう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відображення, картинка, кліп,фото"
    }
]